<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Your awesome title</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 22:08:33 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 22:08:33 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Millennial Curmudgeon Problem</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Last year, a friend of mine who teaches high school mentioned in a Facebook status that all of his students kept using the phrase “on fleek” to describe anything and everything (though typically directed toward eyebrows).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I scoffed to myself and thought about how dumb that sounded and carried on. A few months later, every thing was “on fleek”. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/brandonfleek&quot;&gt;Brands were on fleek&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2015/02/22/upshot/internet-language-quiz.html&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The New York Times&lt;/em&gt; was on fleek&lt;/a&gt;. The phrase had permeated the culture. What I had dismissed as irrelevant a few months before was now the coolest thing in the world (for a while, before cycling right back to uncool again). I had become my father, and “on fleek” was an updated version of some stupid early aughts phrases I threw around. It was off the hook, yo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, maybe not &lt;em&gt;my&lt;/em&gt; father. But &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; father. Our fathers. Society’s fathers. In other words: Somewhere along the line I became dismissive of the preferences of those younger than me. I swore I would never be that close-minded adult. But there I was. I had become Darth Vader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/minecraft.png&quot; width=&quot;780&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; alt=&quot;An old man in Minecraft. Just like me, you whippersnappers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like Social Security and pensions, ignoring the habits and preferences of people younger than ourselves is a luxury that will end with Generation X. Especially those of us in the media/culture/internet business. 20 years ago you could probably coast along and safely disregard trends and still have your job security in tact. No one is saying we late-20-somethings need to run around saying “on fleek”, but each generation brings with it a larger digital audience. We ignore them at our peril.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demographics say that we Millennials are having children later than our parents. This means we have a longer period of our lives where we associate with no children to tie us back to youth culture. So download Minecraft and play around. Subscribe to a few of the YouTube stars. Poke around YikYak. Walk in the footsteps of those younger than you, no matter no foreign their habits may seem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all, there’s some older Baby Boomer who thinks the Internet is a giant waste of time and all of younger folks are just fools. Don’t be that guy. You promised you wouldn’t, remember?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 15:49:30 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/essays/2015/08/20/The-Millennial-Curmudgeon-Problem.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/essays/2015/08/20/The-Millennial-Curmudgeon-Problem.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>essays</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
